[
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
    "answer": "4",
    "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 * 2?",
    "answer": "8",
    "options": ["6", "8", "10", "12"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 * 3?",
    "answer": "12",
    "options": ["10", "11", "12", "13"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 + 8?",
    "answer": "16",
    "options": ["14", "15", "16", "17"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 12 - 7?",
    "answer": "5",
    "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 * 2?",
    "answer": "14",
    "options": ["12", "12", "14", "15"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 - 3 ?",
    "answer": "6",
    "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 + 3 ?",
    "answer": "11",
    "options": ["8", "9", "10", "11"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 - 14 ?",
    "answer": "3",
    "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 * 5 ?",
    "answer": "25",
    "options": ["15", "20", "25", "30"]
  }
]
